# **Tim Schieber**

timothy.schieber@gmail.com

## **EDUCATION**

# **Buena Vista University**

Media Studies with emphasis on Web Design — 2004-2008

Private, four-year university based in Storm Lake, Iowa.

## **SKILLS**

- HTML/CSS/Sass
- JavaScript
- Salesforce Lightning
- Git
- Webpack
- Unit Testing/Cypress
- Documentation
- Accessibility

### SUMMARY

Experienced front end developer and leader committed to maintaining cutting edge technical skills and up-to-date industry knowledge. Team oriented approach with desire to always help others. Ability to communicate across various teams on web development topics. Extensive background aligning complex development projects to client timelines.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Senior Front End Developer, Intouch Solutions

Overland Park, KS — Dec 2021-Present

Developer on multiple global websites. Primary team resource for Salesforce Lightning development and site builds/deployments.

# Digital Delivery Lead, Fishawack Health

Remote — July 2021-November-2021

Lead for a team of producers in charge of running all aspects of digital projects, including creative, UX and development.

## Team Lead, Development Services, Intouch Solutions

Overland Park, KS — Aug 2020-July 2021

Lead for a team of developers building various websites and applications. Responsibilities including estimation, documentation, cross-team collaboration and project deadlines.

### Senior Front End Developer, Intouch Solutions

Overland Park, KS — Aug 2015-July 2020

Senior resource on a large team of developers building applications for pharmaceuticals. Lead on several large projects and helped push processes/standards across teams.

## **User Interface Developer, Level Five Solutions**

Overland Park, KS — Oct 2011-Jul 2015

Front end development of various web applications and sites including mobile and responsive using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and other languages.

Management role for resource planning development team.

# Senior Web Designer, Plattform Advertising

Lenexa, KS- Jun 2008-Sept 2011

Designed and coded marketing websites to be used for paid advertising campaigns. Was involved with leadership meetings for the interactive department.